Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Let's Go
This world is bursting with colors
Truth and lies bewilder our eyes
Use your heart and truly see
Find the truth is right here
Hey you good or bad, true and false
You can't escape this heart's gray smoke
Bring all the courage that you have
Maybe then you can save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Down-and-Out Poet
You're finally here
Wasn't there a new mission today?
Where's Lord Eye?
Lord Yan is currently carrying out his duty as a supermarket stockkeeper, counting inventory.
So the meeting to assign new missions is being pushed back.
As expected of the flawless Lord Eye.
Not only is he full-time and all-around,
he can take on multiple jobs and genuinely complete each one responsibly.
By the way, Dottie, can I ask you something?
What was that big book you were holding just now?
This is a historical testament to the Illumin-Eye's growth.
You want to see it?
Please, please, we absolutely must see it!
Oh, Dottie, you always love keeping us in suspense!
I want to see it too~
Alright, then.
Today, let me tell you
all about the Illumin-Eye, as great as the sun god.
Many years ago,
Lord Eye wasn't like this.
He had just graduated from college.
Full of confidence,
he hoped to become the greatest poet of his time.
He spent his days studying poetry collections
and wrote countless poems himself.
He decided to use his beautiful verses
to celebrate people's lives
and bring them joy.
But,
reality and dreams
are always far apart.
The poems he wrote—
no one liked,
and no one understood them.
No publisher
was willing to work with him.
After being coldly rejected by many publishers
Lord Eye's life
fell into unprecedented hardship
The helpless Lord Eye
could only put his dream aside
and work at a supermarket
to barely scrape by
But no matter how hard life got
Lord Eye refused to stop writing
and kept creating his poetry
But because of this
he often ended up neglecting customers
Sorry
Excuse me, which aisle are the massagers in?
Thanks
I pay you to work here
Not to have you loafing around on the job
You hear me?
You dumb idiot
Someone like you who only eats and shits
and can't do a damn thing
has no point being alive
You might as well drop dead already
Your crappy poems
aren't even worth toilet paper
Even a finger's better.
Sweet potato, potato.
Same kind, stored apart.
I will, again and again,
be dead drunk,
to understand
that life is my endlessness.
Pay up, you scoundrel!
Trying to freeload?
This good-for-nothing came to drink without money.
You're asking for death!
Money doesn't matter.
Where is this place?
This is...
This is something I can't understand at all.
This book seems to be all in ancient Chinese.
What on earth does it mean?
Gah, what am I even doing?
I should find a way out of here first.
A seasoned fisherman can always weather a storm.
It worked! It worked!
Could this be—
As I thought.
As I keep turning the pages of this ancient book
I can see incredible visions
This is the Illumin-Eye Empire
The Illumin-Eye
Legend says the people of the ancient Illumin-Eye kingdom
Once opened the Gate of Ancient Civilization
From then on, the whole nation was filled with joy and happiness
People honored teachers and the Way, and lived with civility and love
And they deeply revered poets who celebrated life
Yet many years later
The prosperous ancient Illumin-Eye kingdom
Was invaded by another island nation
In this war
The Illumin-Eye kingdom was defeated and destroyed
From then on
The Gate of Ancient Civilization was tightly shut
And was never opened again
I see
Now I understand it all
This is it
This is what I've been searching for
This is my great destiny
Wow!!
Ending theme
Saying goodbye to a classic always leaves you with a sense of loss
See tomorrow waving to me upon your horizon
Each day through sunrise and sunset, time spins into even more dreams
Awaiting every second, every moment of life
Bright eyes are shimmering
A smile that greets the sun
Bravely speak that little touch of wonder treasured in your heart
A gentle morning breeze blows in
Carrying away the wishes of all these years
It will quietly wait at the crossroads ahead, oh